Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Let's go!
Aboard the Raging Black Bull, Osta's team charged toward the capital.
Rescue!
I gotcha!
Magic conversion!
They rescued the townspeople.
Osta Cannon!
And returned the Possessed Magic Knights to normal.
All right!
After that, the Black Bulls were greeted once again by Radies, Valtos, and Sally, who are now burning with hatred for Licht.
You're on your way to the royal capital, too, aren't you?
It sounds like we all have the same objective here, so we might as well...
No way!
You need to make up for what you did!
And you can start off by helping us save the Clover Kingdom!
Are you kidding me? There's no way I'm gonna do that!
It's not like I'm playing around to you!
After some convincing from Osta, they agreed to cooperate.
Find you in! We'll go with your squad to the royal capital!
Meanwhile, Longris appeared before several members of the Golden Dawn who had fallen under the possession of elves.
Birds of a twisted feather flock together, I suppose.
I know I'm itching to get my hands around the throats of those despicable royal scum.
The midnight sun is set.
It's time to show humankind the wrath of a brand new Golden Dawn.
Not much longer now.
You worthless humans.
Kind of magia.
You made utilization by Lawrence!
You are freaking lucky, I'm not.
Not much longer now.
eui of crookededor in the green базibal스펅
But they say jolie to explicitate to Rayunden.
Can you give it?
Can you give it to me
This is your way
This is what...
so
Vaud, am I going insane?
Because I don't understand.
Apparently, your son, who engaged in violent behavior during my Royal Knight Selection
exam, is now under suspicion of treason?
I assume there's been some sort of miscommunication.
We agree, Your Majesty.
It's not true.
No one from the House of Vaud would do such a vile thing.
Please believe us.
My dear little Longris is no traitor.
I give you my word, sir.
That may be so, but even if it is a rumor, I can't let my bloodline mix with a man of
such ill repute.
Great Uncle, I know Lord Longris and don't have any misgivings about him.
Please don't judge him too harshly.
Be silent, Phinnes.
Your opinion is of no concern in this matter.
And you two should be ashamed that she even felt the need to defend you!
Yes, this is Lady Phinnes.
She will marry the next head of the House of Vaud.
Nice to meet you.
Pardon the interruption, Your Majesty, but I bring urgent news.
It's a development regarding the mage attacks.
Don't bother!
I'm sure the magic knights have already gathered in the capital.
Until I get there, they can do whatever they want for all I care!
So many Golden Dawn mages.
Why are you in this area?
We are the Castle Knights.
We've got this place under control.
Your group should hurry and help the townspeople.
Actually, we have some business with the humans on the other side of that door.
How dare you make such jokes at a time like this?
Beyond this gate are the castles of three royal families.
Even magic knights need permission to proceed past this point!
A stupid rule made by humans is meaningless and easily broken.
What are you?
Clearing the way.
That's treason!
We'll stop you!
Now, compass magic!
Willful compass!
No! Don't lift him in fast!
This is in your hands.
Understood.
My group and I will focus on the right side.
Sounds good.
We'll take care of the left then.
Which leaves me to charge in from the front.
And slaughter them all.
Stop right there!
Actually, I believe you're the ones who will be stopping.
So Longris did make that hole in the castle gate!
Honestly, I'm not too worried about helping the royals out.
But this key...
Judging by that, some pretty tough contenders have weaseled their way into the castle.
We'll have to let the others take care of the town and fix this ourselves.
Yes, sir!
Here! I got you!
Dark magic!
Dark cloak!
Lightless blood strike!
Man, every one of these guys is overflowing with magic power!
Two of us against dozens of them!
It doesn't look good!
You're not trying to kill us?
You're awfully naive.
Oh, no. I fully intend to kill you.
And by you, I mean the freeloader who took control of that body.
Enough chit-chat!
Dark magic! Black hole!
It's gonna be tricky to beat four of them.
It doesn't matter how many of you there are.
You'll never overpower us!
I recognize that weird magic.
Great job getting possessed, you useless bastards!
But I got to admit it's pretty entertaining!
You're exactly the ones I want to slice up!
So thanks for coming out!
Oh, perfect!
It's Jack the Ripper, Captain of the Green Preying Mantises, and all-around psychopaths!
Good grief.
It's nice to have reinforcements, but did it have to be this guy?
What's wrong, Yami?
Do you want to be the first one to get filleted?
You almost got me that last time, so watch it!
We're lucky they didn't take control of you, String Bean, and we'd all be reduced to shreds by now.
If you think I'd get myself possessed and miss out on the fun, then you're even dumber than I thought!
Humans!
We won't allow any of you to leave alive!
Say goodbye!
Hammering magic!
God's side!
Corundum magic!
Ideal closer!
Those weak blades can't cut through my armor!
Die!
Kick ya!
Touch!
Die!
Shit!
That won't help you.
Your attacks are all so predictable!
You're hanging in the ass!
Dark magic!
Dark close lightless blade storm!
It's taking all I got to stay one step ahead.
Watch for your swing in those things!
Kick ya gear!
Just die!
This is a real blast!
Sounds like Jack's bringing a little extra crazy.
They're both captains and they're still struggling!
Hey Jack!
What's the next idea on that sick old head of yours?
Yeah!
Same thing you're thinking!
And that's suffering magic!
Death side!
I already told you!
Your spells won't work on me!
Agh!
There's nothing in the world that I can't sever!
But are you even worth slashing up?
Prove it to me!
Wait, what?
The property of the magic changed somehow!
Huh?
Somebody's distracted.
Dark magic!
Dark clunk!
Lightless blood strike!
Haha!
That's a big mistake!
Finral!
Yes, sir!
Spatial magic!
Fallen angel gate!
What?
But how?
Alright!
Great job as always, you two!
You're really getting the hang of this stuff, aren't you?
Not too shabby, Finral!
If you can back me up in a fight, you must not be completely incompetent!
Uh, thanks a lot!
Man, this guy's scary!
Hey, that kid's my ride, so try not to freak him out!
Jerk!
They both are!
Come on, let me borrow him sometime!
No way!
Get your own door guy!
This is super fun and all, but we should get going!
Uh, look over there!
Hmm, kek-keh!
Oh!
Why would the Golden Dawn do this?
You're the Magic Knights!
It's your duty to protect the people of the upper class!
Ah!
What is the meaning of this?
Don't they know they're in the Royal Palace?
We gathered here to curry favor with the House of Silva
to see if they would grant us a share of their power!
Must they cause trouble now?
You there!
Lowly servant!
Stand still!
Commoners like you only exist for our benefit!
Now act as my shield!
Hiding yourself won't work!
My needles will never miss you!
Doesn't matter where you run, you're dead!
Makes no difference!
We intend on killing every human in this castle!
Damn it all!
It's not fair!
You really lost to Noelle?
That's pathetic, Solid.
It sounds like you let your guard down for a moment.
Noelle isn't capable of anything that powerful!
Hey, Solid.
You might...
want to block.
Just try to hit me, you pipsqueak!
Do your worst!
You good-for-nothing girls!
Sea Dragons!
Roar!
Curse you, Noelle!
I'll make you pay dearly for this!
Hold on.
Who's out there?
I suddenly feel uneasy.
A night from the Golden Dawn?
This is our castle!
You aren't allowed in here!
That magic power.
You're royals.
Which means you're of that tainted bloodline.
I've come to dispose of you.
Her power's incredible.
Oh my goodness, you don't have any manners at all.
Let us teach you.
Mist magic, Solid Mist clones!
Care to have a bit of fun?
Mist spider's thread!
Marble at the strength of a royal!
That's a commoner for you.
Compass magic, useless north.
I lost?
How?
The clones did nothing to distract her.
She located me effortlessly.
Human techniques are so underhanded.
Oh no, Nebra!
How dare you!
You just attacked a Silva!
You won't get away with that!
Funny.
With royal blood, I thought you'd be more astute.
Wait.
I'm sensing an even more powerful presence outside.
The end of all humanity is close at hand.
KK, I wonder what's inside the big mystery ball.
Whatever it is, I'm ready to liven things up.
I appreciate your positivity and all, but I promise it's bad.
In fact, I'm pretty sure it's the enemy base filled with even more people who want to kill us because that's the kind of day it's been.
Well, that's great.
Who the hell thought it'd be a good idea to invite the giant floating boulder to the party?
But look, a pretty little birdie just showed up, too.
No matter what, the castle will not fall.
The royal family.
Welcome home, fancy pants.
Hey!
Noel!
Look who's down there.
It's the captain.
And wait, Fenril, too?
Captain Jack, as well.
Good to see ya!
Sorry to make you worry about me.
I know it must have been lonely for you when I wasn't...
I wouldn't be worried about you if you were missing for a hundred years.
You're so wimpy!
And I hope you enjoyed your nap while the rest of us were trying to save the kingdom.
Idiot.
I'm really glad he pulled through.
Oh, you poor things.
Waiting for beautiful me to make my spectacular return.
Well, don't worry.
The wait is over.
No one missed you.
Now shut up.
Huh.
I know you.
It's been a while, hasn't it, Captain Crazy?
I decided I would join.
Since you seem to be having so much trouble keeping it together.
What was your name again?
Yeah, yeah.
That's real cute.
But like it or not, I'm a member of your ragtag crew.
And you're the one who gave me this cloak.
So get used to it.
There's nobody for you to blame but yourself.
It sure took you long enough, dumbass.
I was getting tired of waiting.
You better make up for wasting time.
And where have you been, Mr. Silver Eagles?
Did you get held up at a hair appointment or something?
Your house is a mess, so you might want to go take care of that.
Get your butts inside or we're going to hog all the carnage for ourselves.
Such nerve from those without royal blood.
Don't mind them.
For what it's worth, you're one of the few people I've always considered to be beautiful.
Silence.
That does not help.
Do whatever you need to do to fix your house.
We're going to go find old King Clover.
They're strong, so don't be a hero and try and take them down on your own.
Your only goal is to rescue and retreat.
Who the hell died and made you, boss?
Oh, shut up.
None of you idiots is allowed to get killed.
You're the last person I needed to hear that from.
I'm home again.
I never thought it would be under these circumstances, though.
So cruel.
How dare those monsters taint our castle with blood.
They will regret this day.
In case you forgot, I don't give a crap about you stuck-up royals and your fancy digs.
So I'm going to do what I want.
Considering how many we're up against, we've got to move smart.
Hey, wait!
Nobody said you could do that!
Just let him go.
He was selected to become one of the royal knights,
so I'm sure he has his own fighting style.
Ready yourself.
There you are, royals!
You ready for your punishment?
I'd ask you the same, but it appears you're incapacitated.
With fine mana control, he can make free transforming mercury magic work for attack and defense at the same time.
Nozel really is talented.
Mother.
We're going to take down the strongest first.
That's Solid's room!
The magic coming off of those compasses is blocking me from landing at it!
What do I do?
This can't be happening!
Water creation magic!
Sea Serpent's Coils!
This is getting me nowhere!
Now what?
Be careful.
We are royalty, you know!
You mentioned that.
Face your fate.
No!
Nozel, it's you!
And Noel!
Mana skin!
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon's Roar!
I've got her!
Now compass magic!
Willful compass!
She deflected it!
Not even the spell Noel used to defeat me could break through that mana!
I knew you would come.
Thank you, Nozel.
Sincerely.
I can't believe Noel managed a spell like that.
But it still wasn't enough.
I hate to admit it, but in my state I'd only hold them back.
It's better if I just retreat.
Mist magic!
Bewildering Forest of Mist!
All of you will die here.
Compass magic!
Another Atlas!
The only way you're escaping this room alive is if you can defeat me first.
What?
I don't have control of my magic.
This technique forcibly disturbs any and all magic in a given area.
No matter how powerful your own abilities may be, human,
you will never be able to put a scratch on me.
And yet.
My spells will hit you without fail.
Stop her, Nozel!
Please!
Stay there, Solid.
You'd only hold us back as you are now.
I will handle this.
It's okay.
I went through all that training.
I'll succeed.
I can do it.
I won't let you hurt my family anymore!
Let's show her our power, Noel.
The house Silva stands strong.
I won't let you know.
NooFbat thing.
See that.
Oh
See you next time.
Jack the Amazing.
There's nothing that I can't sever.
But are you worth cutting up?
You've got to prove it.
With meat like this, you want to cut it into strips of just the right size.
That's safe.
All right, what's it got next?
Show me your waffet.
The best way to prepare tofu is diced into nice scrumptious little cubes.
Oh, hey, that's how I like my victims too.
Death scythe.
I'm on a roll.
I could carve up stuff all day.
They're supposed to be bite-sized pieces, but I've got a big mouth, so it's tricky.
Death scythe.
Don't let it boil over when you add the miso.
Ta-da!
It's Jack the Ripper's famous pork miso soup.
Oh, no, I forgot to put in the soup.
Stuck!
Once there was a girl called the Steel Warrior Princess, known for dancing gracefully through combat.
Black Clover, page 108, Battlefield Dancer.
Now it is Noelle Silver's turn to dance across the battlefield.